Thank you for watching!
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement by Miku Hatsune
I love you so much it's too strange
If there was another me
I'd be able to protect you even more
I love you so much that I can't do it any more
No matter what I'm doing
I love you so much
I don't want to leave you
I want to be close to you
I can't see you when you're too close
You know what I'm saying?
Humans are a bunch of idiots
I'm sure we're all just a bunch of idiots.
But that's not the point
To this love
If it's your stupidity
I'd accept it all
I'd accept it all.
I'm just being an idiot.
Thank you for always watching me. I'm looking forward to seeing you again in the future.
Hello! Stay, this time with Ayano Kawamura from Angeleum,
I'll be talking with Ayano Kawamura from Angeleum and Hana Goto from Angeleum.
This time, we will be presenting you with these two, so please bear with us until the end.
Please bear with me until the end.
Now, Hana-chan is making her first appearance as an MC for Halo! Please introduce yourself.
I am Hana Goto, a new member of Angelem, from Saitama Prefecture, a junior high school student, 15 years old.
My hobby is playing with cats,
My special skill is to find the good in people.
Please do not hesitate to ask me for help.Please.
So you play with cats, do you have any at home?
Yes, I do. I have three cats at home,
I find it very relaxing to spend time with them,
I get a "wow" feeling.
It's a healing experience.
It's healing, isn't it?
Yes.
Another thing I am good at is finding the good in people,
What? May I ask you what you like about me?
Yes, by all means. By all means.
That's difficult.
What I like about you, Ms. Kawamura, is that you have a very cute voice,
I think her voice is one-of-a-kind, and I think it is a wonderful voice,
I think her voice is one-of-a-kind and wonderful, and even her singing voice is recognizable as hers.
Thank you very much.
And the rest..,
And then..,
Miko!
You have Miko too? I'm so glad.
It's so cute,
I often find myself studying how to present myself,
I'm not sure.
She would look at her part in the mirror and say, "I'm going to do this,
I think it's wonderful that you take your part seriously.
Thank you very much.
The third thing is that you are very fashionable,
I admire your fashionable style.
Thank you very much.
I am so embarrassed to ask this myself, I'm so embarrassed to hear it myself,
I'm getting really hot.
Hallo! Ste. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
By the way, this year's Halo! Ste. is the 500th delivery.
The 500th! That's amazing!
That's amazing.
You've already done it 500 times.
Congratulations!
I remember watching "Halo! I remember watching the unveiling of Ms. Ishiyama's debut with excitement,
I have always loved watching the videos of her unveiling and audition videos,
But this was the first time I saw the announcement of my debut since I joined the trainee group,
I felt that I was the first one to make my debut as a trainee, so I felt like I was the senior,
It was fun.
I think there were a lot of videos of various members' debut on Halo! I think there were a lot of videos of various members' unveiling moments on Halo!
Did you see yours?
I did.
I really saw the moment of my debut on the video,
I thought it was nice to be able to look back on such a moment in my life,
I was happy to see it.
I think it was announced at the "Halo! I think it was announced at the "Halo!
I think it was probably at the Halo! I think I was also announced at the Halloween party.
It's wonderful.
What I remember most is the beginning of the show,
I remember the first time when the members sang solos at various places,
I was really impressed when Takeuchi-san sang "Campus Life".
Also, in the episode in which I performed,
I had dinner with Rumi Tanbo of Juice-Juice,
I was biting an apple when I had dinner with Rumi Tanbo of Juice-Juice.
At that time, I liked apples a lot,
I was like, "I can eat it well. Like, I can eat well.
I said, "Well, try it.
He cracked open an apple,
I was like, "Shirichirichirichirichirichirichirichirichirichiri,
I ate it, leaving only the seeds.
It was very interesting.
Please take a look at the past videos.
Project's latest live videos and the latest information,
Project's latest live videos and information.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Here you go!
Concert in Tokyo
Tokyo today!
Well, welcome back, Momochan!
To be continued.
Matoto!
Ruri!
Hanane!
Hirano!
Nanomi!
Sugaya!
Natsumiya!
Mikoto!
Momo!
Joko!
It was JoJo's March of Chabu-Chabu!
Please!
Chicken
Did you give up your mute too? Did you also give him the silent treatment?
Or a man with a dead weight of love
Even when you're in love with someone you don't know
Sometimes I don't know what to do
Rollygold now, Rollygold now, Rollygold now, Rollygold now, Rollygold now, Rollygold now, find the real thing
Rollygold now Rollygold now I can't help it
Rollygold now, Rollygold now, Rollygold now, Rollygold now, Rollygold now, Rollygold now.
All of it, all of it, just relax.
The earth is cold.
The weather's cold, max.
Fly high, fly high
Exercise, school, hearts, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up
Fly high, high
Most of the time, even if it's your first time
Darlin' Darlin' Darlin'
All the love in the world Darlin'
Oh Oh
Darlin' that sparkles
Don't eat it, be prepared
Love sub pariling' Oh
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
You've got to be right
How can you not be serious, Sally Man?
Why is it that when I'm having a good time
Is interrupted at the end of the day
But liminas, but liminas, but liminas, I'll chickcorn you.
But liminas, but liminas, but seriously, damn it.
But liminas, but liminas, but I want to hear it. It's glorious, isn't it?
Kowho, kowho, kowho, tell him, kowho, kowho, kowho, kowho Koo-hoo, koo-hoo, koo-hoo. Tell her, koo-hoo, koo-hoo.
I don't like it. If you don't mind, bye-bye.
Oh Oh Oh, the true nature of what we're crossing
Oh Oh, romance with you
My first Dance
Darling Darling Darling Me
Darling Darling Darling
Is that what encounters are all about?
Oh Oh Oh, it's perfect
Try Try Try
Oh Oh, it's all right, it's all right
As I'm Leaving
Nobita Baby
If you can see it, it's gone.
Music Miho Nakashima Words and music by Miho Nakashima Arrangement by Miho Nakashima
Sung by Miho Nakashima Sung by Miho Nakashima Sung by Miho Nakashima Sung by Miho Nakashima Sung by Miho Nakashima Sung by Miho Nakashima Sung by Miho Nakashima Sung by Miho Nakashima Miho Nakashima Sung by Miho Nakashima Miho Nakashima Miho Nakashima Sings Miho Nakashima Sings Miho Nakashima Sings Miho Nakashima Sings Miho Nakashima Sings Miho Nakashima Sings Miho Nakashima
Be strong and be a cue ball
You'll clear up the race you foolishly get
What is that, a secret from you
I'm sure you'll stay like you've never found it
I'm sure I could have played the part, but I couldn't hold on to you
It's been a special day
The object has it already
Thanks, but no thanks
Lovey Dovey Lovey
Lovey Dovey Dovey Dovey
All the Love in the World
Dainai Oh Oh Dainai Oh Oh
Surely Forever
Dainai Oh Oh
Dainai
Be prepared Be prepared
How crazy was that?
I am now a beaver at heart
Thank you very much.
Let's work hard together tomorrow!
This message is brought to you by Ayano Kawamura and
and Kotohana of Angstrom
Halo! stay!
From now on, I'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Let's get started.
It's been about 5 months since you joined Angulum.
What was the most shocking moment for you? What was the most shocking experience for you?
Well, they were so cheerful and noisy in the dressing room and everywhere else.
What was the moment when you felt "I'm a member of Angulum! What was the moment when you felt "I'm a member of Angulum"?
When I saw the audience on the stage for our debut.
What do you want to accomplish as a member of Angelem?
To stand together on a big stage and give a great performance.
What kind of idol do you want to be?
I want to be a sparkling idol who can bring smiles, energy, courage and power to everyone.
Hello! Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year!
Which Hello! Project songs that you listened to for the first time?
It was HELP ME by Morning Musume。 s HELP ME!
Oh!
Wow.
Yes, yes it is.Yes I did.
I joined Angulum! What made me feel that I joined Angstrom?
I felt it on stage when the audience was watching you?
Yes.
I was really moved, and I felt that I had worked so hard since I became a trainee to see you on this stage.
That's right. You were crying with joy, weren't you?
Yes, I was.
But it was a big wow. You must have been happy that everyone was so jubilant.
I was happy.
The first song you listened to was Maama Morimi's "Help Me,
How and when did you hear it, and what made you decide to listen to it?
My mother was the first person to listen to Morning Musume。 I was a child when I heard Morning Musume,
I had heard of Morning Musume when I was little. I had heard of Morning Musume when I was little,
I had heard of Morning Musume when I was little, but at the time I thought it was about a group of girls who took on the fierceness of cows,
But after listening to HELP ME, I found out that they were actually an idol group like that,
Oh, wow.
Yes, that's true. If I had called them Morning Musume without knowing anything about them, I would have thought that they were just another idol group. If I had called them "Morning Musume" without knowing anything about them, I would have thought, "Oh, my God,
I thought, "I'm already an old man.
You must think I'm an old man.
Yes, that's true.
That's for sure.
I'm glad I got to listen to Help Me.
Yes, it was. It was good.
Saya Tamura's question will be asked after the VTR!
Hallo! Ste! Wake up! Call!
Wake up! Call! It's time to wake up!
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart
Just do it, just do it, just do it, just do it
Just do it! Just do it! Just do it! The darkness of the night, just waiting for the morning
I'll light up that heart
Dance baby!
Morning Musume。 Wake up! Call!
Wake up!
October 25 On sale!
Hallo! Ste!
I would like to ask Mr. Kawamura a question next.
Please give me your best regards.
What do you recommend this time of year in Kochi, your hometown of Autumn in Triangle?
Mitaka pears.
Pears.
Pears~.
So crunchy!
What is your favorite road you recently encountered?
When I went to Dogo Hot Springs in Ehime Prefecture, there was a road that looked like colorful flowers,
It was so beautiful.
I would like to see it.
Please give us a copy of "11 members who are perfect for the current Angelem.
They are the 11 members of Angulum.
How would you describe Angelem in one word?
Love!
Which Hello! Project song do you dislike and would like to perform someday?
Smileage's Smile Beauty.
There are a few things I like about it,
It's a copy of 11 rounded people, perfect for Angstrom,
Now that's right. Angstrom is going on a tour called "11 Angstrom,
So, we are the 11 members of Angstrom,
So we are the 11 members.
Everyone is working very hard to deliver that concert, Everyone worked very hard to deliver that concert,
I think the sense of unity of the 11 members has come out more,
I think that the sense of unity of the eleven members, or
So here is a copy of it.
It's wonderful.
Yes, it is. One more thing.
Project, which song would you like to perform someday?
I love S/mileage so much,
I loved S/mileage so much that when I was in elementary school, my classmates and I listened to many of their songs,
One of their songs is called Smile Bijin,
One of the songs is called "Smile Bijin," and I'm not sure what it's about,
One of the songs was called "Smile Bijin," and the lyrics were very cute and showed a little bit of a student's bullishness,
I've never sung the song, so I'd like to sing it someday,
I've never sung it, so I'd like to sing it someday.
I've never sung it before, so I'd like to sing it someday.
Let's do it.
Let's do it. Stay tuned for more.
Next time preview
Masashi Natsuyaki
Here we go, Hello Kitchen!
This time, we have these members here!
Please give them a warm welcome.
I'm Sakura Oda from Morning Musume。 23, Sakura Oda.
Actually, I'm Sakura Oda, a member of Morning Musume。 I've never been to Hello Kitchen since Morning Musume。 I've never participated in Hello Kitchen since Morning Musume。
Actually, it will be my 11th anniversary on the day of this photo shoot.
I'm very nervous because this will be my 11th anniversary and the first time I'm going to showcase my cooking skills.
I will do my best while having fun!
Thank you very much for your time.
Now, what would you like to cook this time?
Yes, I would like to make chawanmushi.Yes, I would like to make chawanmushi
And?
Yes, sir.
I will make stuffed green pepper.
This time, I'd like to do my best to make two dishes.
First of all, here are the ingredients
Chawanmushi was Oda-chan's request this time.
Why did you request steamed egg custard this time?
Yes, I also consider chawanmushi to be a complete meal in my opinion.
I often make it myself, but
I often make it myself.
Oh, I see.
Chawanmushi is really easy to make, or rather, it's simple, which is why it's so difficult.
I'm pretty much self-taught, so
I thought there must be a better chawanmushi.
I'm going to teach you how to make it.
If you leave the whole thing to me...
Well, I'm not that good at Japanese food.
I'm doing it at my office, but...
It's not that it's difficult, it's just that it's so simple.
Yes, that's right.
That's why we're cooking together today.
Like a study group.
Yes, that's good, that's good.
Chawanmushi study group.
Okay, so there are two dishes.
Let's do our best.
I look forward to working with you.
Please do.
Please do. Yes, please.
So, doctor, what would you like to make first?
First, I'd like to prepare the ingredients for the chow mein.
Today I'm preparing this.
I brought some raw shrimp.
Take the back skin off, take the shells off, and take the legs off.
It's better to boil them with the back skin removed and the shells on.
Take off the shell, and take off the legs.
Oh, I can remove the shell.
It's done.
I was told to add a little sake and salt to the water as it boils.
A little bit, about a tablespoon.
A tablespoon?
A little more
OK.
Now it's boiling.
Turn off the heat and put in the shrimp.
Put the lid on and wait for about 5 minutes.
Shrimps are spicy and flavorful.
I see.
I want you to remember that.
And the same goes for vegetables.
If you boil them with a lot of salt, the color will be more vivid.
How about shrimp?
They're good after five minutes.
Nice aroma.
Shall we break up the crab cakes?
Unfortunately, this is not real crab.
It's a crabcake. It's a crabcake.
Do you want me to break it up?
Break them into pieces.
They'll spread when you put the egg mixture in.
Okay, now the kamaboko.
When you put it in, it's jagged.
Like this.
Put it in first.
Don't put it here.
Jagged, jagged, jagged, jagged.
Finally, do it like this.
A little bit on the side.
Not much, but it's not done?
Is it working? I'd like it better.
Maybe a little thinner.
It's hard! This is the most amazing technique in Japanese food.
It's not done at all.
Then let's leave it here.
Then please put 300cc of water.
And a teaspoon of soy sauce.
And mirin (sweet cooking rice wine).
Mirin (sweet cooking rice wine): 1 teaspoon.
And 1 teaspoon of soup stock.
As long as it's dissolved, it'll be fine.
Yes.
Just warm it up a little and it should be fine.
Now it's melted.
Okay.
If it's too hot, the eggs will burn.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
I'll let this cool.
Yes, sir.
You're good. You're used to eggs.
Here's a point for you, Mr. Miyagi. Mix without whisking.
Why don't you whisk it?
Because he's a buster.
When it's done, the bubbles will make a hole.
But you want to cut it well. Can't you do it horizontally?
I was told to cut the egg yolk with the chopsticks on the side of the egg yolk.
And the yolk is about to go soft.
So you cut the white meat with the chopsticks, like you're cutting the elastic part of the white meat.
That's what I usually do.
I've made a lot of mistakes.
I've made a lot of mistakes
I put it in the rah station.
It smells so good!
When you make soup stock, you think, "I'm so glad I'm Japanese.
I think it's good for miso soup.
We have to peel the prawns first.
Remove the tails, too.
Yes.
And the comer's good, too.
I think it's going to hit me... or maybe it's going to flap around inside.
And finally, Mitsuba... this one's cosmetics size, right?
I'm nervous... about 7 minutes...
It's about 7 minutes.
It looks good.
I'm so relieved.
Now, please put this in.Now put this in.
It's okay, I'm putting out the fire now.
Okay.
Let go.
The lid, it won't close.
This was just a perfect fit,
It's important to open this gap.
Sakura, you're looking at it all the time.
Look, it's already with a clear lid,
It's a pudding container,
It's transparent,
Why look at it like that,
The top is aluminum, but you can see it from the side.
When it hardens properly, it tilts a little.
That's right.
It tilts and hardens.
Look at that,
It shrinks a little more, doesn't it?
It shrinks and a little liquid comes out on the outside.
It's clear.
That's about it.
You can shake it and so on.
And then, you can slant it,
If you put it at an angle,
The surface, or rather, the top part,
I can see that the top part is about to spill out,
It's not in yet.
If it is quite elastic, it should be fine.
Let's take a look.
Shall we take a look? Do you want to see it?
That way.
Over there.
It's hot.
How is it?
I think I can get in.
Next time.
I think I'm done with this one.
I'll be most attentive.
I think this one is fine.
It looks good.
It's very resilient.
Yes, it does.
We have this one, too.
Please open it.
It's so beautiful.
Smell.
It smells really good.
It smells so good.
It's great.
It went better than I expected.
Success.
It's done.
So, that's it,
This time, the chawanmushi was completed,
We will have a tasting next time.
Next time, we will also make stuffed peppers,I'm also planning to make stuffed peppers next time,
Please look forward to that too.
Looks delicious.
I'll have some.
I'm so happy! Delicious!
Wow!
I want to make it!
I learned a lot!
Yes!
Well, I have a new favorite menu item.
Oh! Yes!
It's called eggplant tataki.
Yes!
Deep fry the eggplant with a little bit of broth.
Then chop shiso leaves, myoga and green onion and put them on top.
Yes!
Drizzle some yuzu ponpon on it and eat it.
Sounds delicious!
It's so delicious!
Yes!
I've been deep-frying and eating it a lot since the summer!
Wow! I love it! Please make it next time!
I'll make it! I'll make it!
Yay!
But it was really delicious.
I ate it all the time!
It was really delicious!
Please make it and try it!
Hana-chan
Do you have a favorite dish that you have made? Do you have a favorite dish that you have made?
I like macarons.
Macarons?
You made macarons?
Yes!
Wow!
I was into baking for a while.
I made them at that time.
They were so hard to make.
Macarons are the most difficult of all sweets.
That's right! They're super hard.
But I made a few more, making many mistakes.
Were you good at it?
A little! It looks like...
They weren't very pretty, but
But the macarons I made tasted amazing!
They taste even better when you make them yourself!
Yes!
Make and bring macarons sometime!
Yes! I will!
I'm looking forward to it!
Hallo! Sta.
With Ayano Kawamura from Angulum,
Goto Hana of Angstrom's "Halo! STE!
I'd like you to get to know Hana-chan a little better,
I'd like to go a little deeper into Hana-chan.
I've asked her manager about episodes of Hana Goto's life,
Here are some of them.
I'm scared.
Okay, I'll start. I'll go then.
Where I think Goto Hana is strange, I hear that she can see numbers that can read people's aura.
I wonder what numbers Kawamura and the other members can see.
What does it mean to be able to read a person's aura?
I can sense a person's atmosphere by their color,
I can sense a person's mood by their color,
I think, "This person has this kind of color," or "This person has this kind of number.
For example, I think of a member of Angelem as having this kind of color or this person as having this kind of number.
Kawamura-san is 7.
7!
My birthday is July 7,
Lucky 7. It's my favorite number.
That's great!
I'm so happy.
That's great.
That's great. That's amazing.
I did it~!
I'm so happy.
Ask me more. What color do you see?
It's a beautiful color, like a little Bordeaux red, or a mature reddish brown, or a mixture of brown and brown.
Wow! That's unexpected.
It's the first time I've been told that color. I am very happy.
Here is my episode.
There are many things that I think are very serious,
I'm currently on a concert tour, and during rehearsals,
I know that you learned a lot of songs at once during rehearsals.
When I received advice from my seniors, teachers, etc., I made sure to put it into practice,
I put it into practice and tried this one. I was able to do this. I tried this one,
I tried this thing you mentioned the other day. I tried it,
I was very impressed by the fact that he was able to communicate the process,I am very impressed with the way they communicate the process,
I think it's very impressive.
I'm glad.
There are some things that are really strange to me,
But I can sense from various aspects that she is very serious about her work,
I am looking forward to working with Hana-chan more and more.
Thank you very much.
Let me greet everyone once again.
Yes, I'm Hana-chan. I am a new member of Angelem.
I'm from Saitama Prefecture. I am 15 years old and a junior in high school.
From now on, I would like to do my best as a member of Angelem,
I will do my best to make everyone happy by showing my personality.
I will do my best to make everyone happy. Project 25 last month.
Project 25th Anniversary Concert was held last month.
Looking back on the two days, were there any impressive moments backstage?
Yes, there were. I had a chance to see the rehearsal,
When Mr. Nakazawa was rehearsing his solo,
Project members, and also OJ and other staff members,
Project members, OJ, and other staff members were sitting in the audience watching the rehearsal,
At that time, Mr. Nakazawa waved to us as we were walking down the flower aisle,
When we waved, he waved back.
I was so happy,
I was so happy, and I was so excited and happy.
It was really nice.
When I am not on stage,
I have a monitor, and we all watch the monitor together,
I can hear the live singing, but I can't hear the audience,
I was wearing ear monitors, so I could hear the live singing,
I was listening to them while thinking how cool they were.
It was a very nice concert.It was a very nice concert.
It was wonderful.
This time, from the Hello! Project 25th Anniversary Concert,
Project 25th Anniversary Concert.
You performed with the current members and OJ members Akari Takeuchi and Rina Katsuta,
Hana-chan, this was your first time to perform with them.
How did you like it?
I was very happy to be able to perform with them,
And "Red Earphones" is a really cool song,
I had a lot of fun.
For "Aka Earphones," Mr. Case performed as a soloist,
Katsuta's solo was the original,
It had been a long time since I heard those two sing together,
I thought, "Wow, this is it! Red earphones! I thought,
I was so happy while performing with them.
What was the other thing that impressed me during rehearsals?
I was so impressed during rehearsals that I thought Takeuchi-san and Katsuta-san were also members of the group,
They seemed to be at ease with the other members during their free time.
I thought, "Oh, that's Katsuta. It was like I was Katsuta-san.
The sense of distance between us was as close as that of the members,
He was very kind and talked to me about many things,
I was very happy,
And Mr. Takeuchi, you know,
Takeuchi-san said, "The rows here are a little bit irregular, so you should straighten them up,
Mr. Takeuchi-san told me that the horizontal rows were a bit disorganized and I should align them better, or that I should play this part more rhythmically,
You also gave me advice on the performance aspect,
I think we were able to give a performance in which we all worked together.
Please have a look at the performance.
Here we go!
♪♪♪ ♪♪♪
I avoid love, but his love pushes me away
Bold feelings are tinged with affection
I was hoping for a doomed love
But in reality, I don't rely on my heart Whenever he gets jealous
Whenever he's jealous of my calls or checks on me
I don't want to be with him anymore
I just want to listen to something upbeat
I pulled out the earpiece from the bottom of my bag
The red thread that's tangled up in my head
I felt the need to untangle the tangled red thread
It's the age of wireless, right?
Not to mention human emotion.
Women are no longer bound by the wiles of men.
It's all so different, isn't it? And human love, I don't need to tell you.
But somewhere I'm still dreaming of that invisible red thread that connects our hearts
I'm a love phobic, but I'm trapped in this love.
The day my emotions turned to love...
Dusk is falling and you're confessing
But I'm not fooling around with Big
I'm afraid you won't like me
I'm afraid that you and I will meet an AI
The sight of my honest self
my room, your parting words
Your back, the earphones I'd forgotten
The red thread that didn't fall off
We're still there
It's Booth's time, isn't it?
I don't have to tell you... human emotion.
Of men. A man's kindness
Women are no longer bound by the kindness of men.
It's the age of Bluetooth, of course, and human affection.
But somewhere I believe in you and the bright, indelible thread that connects us.
In the age of Bluetooth, I'm sure you're not the only one who believes in human affection.
VOCALS, helping out!
When?
Don't you die?
Don't be intimidated. Don't feel limited by interest rates.
No more men's selfishness.
Women are no longer bound by the whims of men.
White eyes
Don't you die?
No more intimidation, no more interest-rate love
But somewhere inside you're still dreaming
An invisible red thread that connects our hearts
Thank you for your work
With Aino Kawamura of Angulum,
Hanon Wada of Angeleum, and STE, presented by Aino Kawamura of Angelem and Kanon Wada.
It's time for the ending of the show!
Yes, this is Kanon-chan's first time to appear on Halo! Stage for the first time, Hanon!
How did you feel when you were MC for the first time?
Well, I really wanted to do Halo! I've wanted to do this for a long time.
I was very happy to be able to do it.
It was my first time to MC at Halo! I was happy to be able to do it with Mr. Kawamura.
I was happy to be able to do it with Mr. Kawamura.
I'm so happy.
I feel so relieved, don't you?
Thank you.
I also had a great time MCing with Kanon-chan. I also had a great time MCing with Hanae-chan!
I'm very happy.
Here's an announcement!
Angulum Concert Tour 2023 Autumn
The 11 members of Angelem are now holding a concert tour!
The next concert will be in Fukuoka!
We also have shows in Hokkaido, Okinawa, and Osaka!
Please come and see us if you are in the area!
And on November 24th, we will be performing at the Nippon Budokan!
This will be the first Budokan performance for Yukiho and Hana Goto in Shimoita.
So we are very much looking forward to it!
Countdown Japan on December 29th
Angelem will perform on 2324!
I'm really very, very
I'm really grateful for that, and
I'm so grateful for this opportunity, and I'm sure everyone will do their best.
The "Hello! Project members will appear more and more on this channel!
Project members will be uploading new videos every Wednesday.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Our partners were Ayano Kawamura and Hana Goto from Angulum!
Good bye!